<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="253828F5-0EA1-46F1-9D55-E8B17C156FEC">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20100330" date="2010-03-30 00:48:58 -0400"/>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="30_Photo_of_the_Day_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="585px" height="365px"/>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Yesterday I began two projects and continued a third working with Patrick Raymond of Raymond Guitars (also my band mate!)&#xD;&lt;b&gt;I continued work on building my lap steel...&#xD;I have been working on this for a couple of years now as a side project...&#xD;of course once it's finished I have to learn to play it!&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;I also started two other projects...&#xD;I began a neck reset project on my 1980 Martin D-28-12 guitar.&#xA0; &#xD;It is my hope to get this fixed once and for all and make it playable again, &#xD;and learn a lot from Patrick in the meantime!&#xA0; As you can see in the picture, &#xD;I got so excited about getting the project started that I removed the 4th fret instead of the 15th fret as Patrick had instructed...but it's okay, they all get replaced before the job is finished!&#xA0; The 15th fret gets removed so we can drill a hole for a small needle to be inserted into the neck joint to inject steam into the joint, melting the glue and allowing us to remove the neck for the badly needed "reset."&#xA0;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;Lastly, we started refurbishing an old neck I had built which I will use on a solid body electric I have had in my mind for quite some time.&#xA0; The first step was to remove the old heel and then remove all of the frets to re-radius the fingerboard from flat to a 16" radius.&#xA0; Here is a picture of a few of the steps:&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Guitar Building News!</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Tuesday, March 30, 2010</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
